Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of Research, Graduate Policy Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of Research, Graduate Policy records
1984-2002
SC1110
Stanford University. Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of Research.
1.5 Linear feet (1 box)
.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The collection was transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of Research in 2012.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
.
Scope and Contents
.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of Research.
Collection Contents
- Graduate Division Administrative Manual, 1988 Sep (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Graduate student salary rates, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Black Graduate Student Association (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Escondido Village infill housing (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Graduate housing expansion plan, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Graduate housing issues, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Graduate student housing tour, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Graduate housing survey and results, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Graduate housing recommendation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Housing report, Advistory Committee for New Housing for Graduate Students, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Project Program, Graduate Student Housing at Governor's Corner, draft, 1994 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Axess 2000 Project, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Axess 2000 Project, 1999 Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Axess 2000 Project, 1999 Jan 11 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Axess 2000 Project, 1998 Oct 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Axess 2000 Project: Phase 1, 1998 Mar 4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Axess 2000 Project, Executive Steering Committee, 1999 Mar 22 (Box 1, Folder 19)